{
    "subject": "resource/Zhejiangosaurus",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Zhejiangosaurus (meaning \"Zhejiang lizard\") is an extinct genus of nodosaurid dinosaur from the Upper Cretaceous (Cenomanian stage) of Zhejiang, eastern China. It was first named by a group of Chinese and Japanese authors Junchang L\u00fc, Xingsheng Jin, Yiming Sheng and Yihong Li in 2007 and the type species is Zhejiangosaurus lishuiensis (\"from Lishui\", Chinese administrative unit on which the fossil was found). It has no diagnostic features, and thus is a nomen dubium.",
    "human_readable": "Zhejiangosaurus is an extinct genus of nodosaurid dinosaur from the Upper Cretaceous (Cenomanian stage) of Zhejiang, eastern China.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8171201944351196,
            "question": "What characteristics might distinguish Zhejiangosaurus from other nodosaurids?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7792233228683472,
            "question": "To what specific group of dinosaurs does Zhejiangosaurus belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7346105575561523,
            "question": "Why is it important to study extinct dinosaurs like Zhejiangosaurus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7229915261268616,
            "question": "In which part of the world were Zhejiangosaurus fossils found?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7105652093887329,
            "question": "During which geological period did Zhejiangosaurus live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.63262540102005,
            "question": "What is the geological age of the fossil discoveries of Zhejiangosaurus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6170507073402405,
            "question": "Can you name any other dinosaurs that lived during the same period as Zhejiangosaurus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5851607918739319,
            "question": "What type of environment would Zhejiangosaurus have inhabited?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49805590510368347,
            "question": "How do scientists reconstruct the appearance and behavior of dinosaurs like Zhejiangosaurus?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41164472699165344,
            "question": "What is the name of the dinosaur genus being described?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Zhejiangosaurus is an extinct genus of nodosaurid dinosaur from the Upper Cretaceous (Cenomanian stage) of Zhejiang, eastern China.",
            "html": "dbpedia_622_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How do scientists reconstruct the appearance and behavior of dinosaurs like Zhejiangosaurus?",
            "html": "dbpedia_622_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of environment would Zhejiangosaurus have inhabited?",
            "html": "dbpedia_622_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any other dinosaurs that lived during the same period as Zhejiangosaurus?",
            "html": "dbpedia_622_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_622_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_622_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_622_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_622_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_622_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_622_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_622_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_622_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_622_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_622_55.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe provided context information confirms that Zhejiangosaurus is indeed an extinct genus of nodosaurid dinosaur from the Upper Cretaceous (specifically the Cenomanian stage) of Zhejiang, eastern China. This aligns with the query statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}